experts123.com 2016-03-08

# Experts123 - Privacy Policy

**Effective October, 2008**

Welcome to Experts123, LLC and Experts123.com. Please read this Privacy Policy. Please read our Terms and Conditions of Use carefully before using or obtaining any content, products or services through our Website(s).

##  Your IP Address

Like most e-commerce websites, each time you visit our Website(s), we automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. In order to administer and optimize our Website(s) for you and to diagnose problems with our Website(s), we use your IP address to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you.

##  Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Like most websites, we use cookies to keep track of your activity on our Website(s) and enhance your experience. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password, and if you choose, to save other personal and financial information so you do not have to re-enter it each time you visit our Website(s). A cookie may also be placed by our advertising server. Such cookies are used for purposes of tracking the effectiveness of advertising served by us on our. Similarly, a cookie may be placed by our third-party advertising companies. If you wish to disable these cookies, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how. However, if you set your browser to disable cookies, you may not be able to access certain areas or features of the Website(s).

##  Other Information We Collect

When browsing our Website(s), you are not required to provide any personal information unless and until you choose to sign up for one of our Experts123 features or other services as described below. We do not knowingly permit our Website(s) to be used by any person under the age of eighteen and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children (meaning those younger than thirteen years of age). We store the data we collect on our own servers and on servers owned by others. We undertake ongoing efforts to assure the integrity and security of the data on our servers, but cannot guarantee that the security measures we employ will always be completely effective. We also cannot guarantee the absolute security of data we store on servers owned by others. We will provide notice on our Website(s) if we have reason to believe the integrity of our stored data has been breached or compromised, potentially permitting unauthorized third-parties to access the stored data.

##  Registered User Information

If you choose to become a Registered User of Experts123.com you must provide your name, address, e-mail address, a unique login name, password, and password validation, and a password hint to help you remember your password. This information is collected on the registration form for several reasons including: (1) personal identification; (2) to allow us to contact you for customer service purposes, if necessary; (3) to customize the content of our Website(s) to meet your specific needs; and (4) to make product improvements to our Website(s).

##  Automatic Logging of Session Data

We automatically log generic information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which we call "session data", that is anonymous and not linked to any personal information. Session data consists of things such as IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the user while on our Website(s). An IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the Internet, such as our web servers, know where to send data back to the user, such as the pages of the website the user wishes to view. We collect session data because it helps us analyze such things as what items visitors are likely to click on most, the way visitors are clicking through the website, how many visitors are surfing to various pages on the website, how long visitors to the website are staying and how often they are visiting. We also record the URLs (Uniform Resource Locators) of the websites you have visited prior to arriving at our Website(s) and the URLs of the destinations you visit after you leave our Website(s). Collecting this information also helps us diagnose problems with our servers and lets us better administer our systems. You should know it is possible to determine from an IP address a visitor's Internet Service Provider (ISP) and the approximate geographic location of his or her point of connectivity. Third-party advertising companies may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of ads.

##  Telephone Tracking Data

If a user (including both Registered Users and visitors) places a telephone call to a number provided by our Website(s), we and/or our advertising partners may record, track and or meter the telephone number of originating the call on our own behalf or on behalf of others offering products or services on our Website(s). We and/or our advertising partners may also store referring telephone numbers.

##  Other

From time to time we may add or enhance services available on our Website(s). To the extent these services are provided and used by you, we will use the information you provide to facilitate the service requested. For example, if you email us with a question, we will use your email address, name, nature of the question, etc. to respond to your question. We may also store such information to assist us in making our Website(s) the better and easier to use.

##  Information Other Websites Collect From You

On our Website(s), we place links to other web sites operated by other parties. Some of these other web sites contain our brand names and trademarks and other intellectual property that we own; others do not. When you click on these links and visit these other web sites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand names, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we do not control these other web sites or these other web sites' business practices, and that this privacy policy does not apply to these other web sites. Consequently, the operators of these other web sites may collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on our Website(s). We encourage you to review their privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for their actions.

##  Sharing Your Information

When you use our Website(s) or provide us with information, we may share personal information among our corporate affiliates at Experts123, LLC. including, but not limited to our affiliates. For example, if you submit a review or rating, we may share your review with our other Website(s), as well as unaffiliated users of such data including suppliers, advertisers, affiliates and other current and potential business partners. We may also use such aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their web sites. Occasionally, we may hire a third party to act on our behalf for projects such as market-research surveys and will provide information to these third parties specifically for use in connection with these projects.

In addition to the circumstances described above, we may disclose your information as part of a validation process in the interest of preventing fraud, to provide proper accounting to our business partners (for advertising listings and related programs) and to validate our business metrics including number of clicks, referrer logs and other tracking information. We may also disclose your information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect our rights or properties of our affiliated companies or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. In addition, if Experts123, LLC or substantially all of its assets are acquired, our customer information will most likely also be transferred in connection with such acquisition.

##  Demographic Information and Saved Listings

We use demographic and listing information to customize our Website(s) and communications to the interests of our users. We may share demographic information and relevant data with advertisers and other third parties so that they can target their advertisements and communications to the appropriate audience. Demographic and listing data we provide to advertisers and other third parties may be linked to information you have provided as a Registered User so that advertisers and third parties can target the offerings presented to you. We may capture, correct, enhance, extrapolate and store additional information and data based on information you supply, including without limitation data relating to your geographic location, IP address and provider, email and other demographic information. We may also enhance the information we collect from you with additional information collected by third parties to correct, match, enhance or complete the data you have provided. We may store and share this enhanced information on an individual or aggregated basis.

##  How We Use Public Information, Reviews, Ratings and Registered User Names

When you become a Registered User, you must enter a user name. Our Website(s) provide you with the opportunity to give reviews, opinions and ratings. Your Registered User name and information may appear next to your content, ratings, questions, answers, guides links and other submitted content as they are posted on our Website(s). Your Registered User name and information may also appear on a Registered User Profile section of our Website(s). We may also use and disclose your Registered User name, information and reviews and ratings in any other manner. To read further details about how we may use your user name, information and reviews, see our Terms of and Conditions of Use.

##  Opt Out

At any time, you can unsubscribe being a Registered User by clicking on the "cancel account" link and following the instructions. We reserve the right to limit our Registered Users to those who provide us with a valid email address and agree to accept e-mails. Registered Users will be notified via e-mail prior to any actions taken.

After you submit personal information in connection with becoming a Registered User or other programs (such as discount or rewards programs), offered or sponsored by third parties on our Website(s), we may use such information to send you marketing emails. However, if we do so, we will provide a link that you can click on to opt-out of receiving subsequent marketing emails generated from the same such information.

Please note that changing or deleting your information otherwise opting-out of receipt of email communications from us will only change or delete the data for purposes of future activity on our Website(s) and for managing future communications. These changes and deletions will not change or delete information that we may have already forwarded to our affiliates or any other third parties, all as provided above in this privacy policy. This includes any reviews, ratings or other user-generated data previously provided to us.

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, the practices of our Website(s), or your dealings with the Website(s), you can contact us as indicated below:

E-mail: [customerservice@experts123.com](mailto:customerservice@experts123.com)

Mailing address: 

Experts123, LLC

PO Box 251942  
Los Angeles, CA 90025
